ACTWU President Jacob Sheinkman Files 5619/004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ACTWU President Jacob Sheinkman Files
1896-1999
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union (ACTWU)
Sheinkman, Jacob
5619/004
200.5 cubic feet
200.5 linear ft.
Records (documents), correspondence.
7297023
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
T. Rucker, January 31, 2011
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 21, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, the most significant union representing workers in the men's clothing industry, was founded in New York City in 1914 as a breakaway movement from the United Garment Workers. Radical and immigrant workers in the tailors' and cutters' locals were the core of the seceding group, which advocated industrial unionism and economic strikes in opposition to the UGW's craft organization, which they saw as conservative and timid. Their diverging views had come to the fore during the historic 1910 dispute at the Chicago firm Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. The opposition called the strike against the UGW leadership's advice, and reached a path-breaking agreement with management that established an arbitration system to settle disputes.
Members flocked to the new union. Around 50,000 strong at its founding, by 1920 the ACWA counted about 170,000 members. Initially composed mostly of immigrants of Jewish European descent with Socialist leanings, the ACWA quickly welcomed members of a great number of nationalities and diverse backgrounds. Like in other garment unions, most workers and many members were women, but the leadership was predominantly male, a situation that did not change for many decades. Early on the union adopted a centralized administrative structure combined with industrial unionism, with the joint boards' by-laws having precedence over those of locals.
Espousing a philosophy perhaps brought over by its early immigrant socialist members, the Amalgamated went beyond bread and butter issues and adopted a distinctive form of social unionism that was largely absent in the American labor movement. Starting in the 1920s, it provided educational opportunities and recreational facilities for its members, as well as services such as an insurance plan, banks offering personal loans at low interest rates, low-cost housing cooperatives, medical clinics, and even union-owned restaurants.
Sidney Hillman was the first president of the new union and the most important officer in its history. He applied his experience as bargaining representative in Chicago to the whole industry. Under his leadership the union made significant strides in securing better wages and working conditions for its members, and at the same time it consolidated gains and provided stability to the industry through the widespread adoption of the arbitration system tested at Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. Hillman paid close attention to industry issues, such as production, pricing, and marketing. In order to help management meet the competition of non-union firms, the union conducted studies of efficiency, work methods, and factory costs. Letters to the official publication of the union, Advance, document the controversy that ensued within the union over what was perceived to be collaboration with management.
Hillman also understood the importance of labor's involvement in national affairs and political action. In the 1920s the ACWA sent delegates to the Conference for Progressive Political Action and to the Farmer-labor party conventions. Although many members and officers were Socialists, the union stopped short of officially endorsing the party. Communist attempts at gaining influence within the union were firmly curbed. Hillman's participation in national affairs and politics became prominent during the New Deal, when he became a close advisor to Franklin D. Roosevelt on labor and economic issues. He also served on the board of the National Recovery Administration. Later, during World War II, he helped establish the Labor's Non Partisan League. He was also named associate director of the Office of Production Management, which assisted in mobilizing the nation's resources for the war effort. Hillman's prestige perhaps reflected the healthy condition of his union, which by the end of the conflict was strong and stable.
During the post World War II period the union faced a number of significant challenges. Membership continued to grow (peaking at 395,000 in 1968), but the union's political influence and visibility in national affairs declined. In their never ending pursuit of lower production costs, many firms relocated to the South, forcing the union to engage in large organizing efforts. Simultaneously, signs began to appear of changes that would lead to the almost complete demise of the domestic apparel industry and, ultimately, to the erosion of union membership. Foreign imports of cheap clothing goods steadily grew in the 1950s and 1960s, and mushroomed in the following two decades, plunging employment in the apparel sector into a steady decline. Union efforts to stem the tide included Buy American campaigns and extensive lobbying in Congress, but they were to no avail. In 1976, the ACWA merged with the Textile Workers of America to become the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Despite successful and much publicized nationwide actions such as the Farah boycott and the J.P. Stevens corporate campaign, the woes threatening the union's existence continued unabated. The fate of the domestic industry was sealed in the late 1970s and the 1980s by the flight of firms chasing tax breaks and cheap labor abroad. By 1995, when ACTWU voted to merge with the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, their combined membership was 350,000. The new Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE!) seemed poised to infuse new life in a troubled union.
Biographical / Historical
Jacob Sheinkman (1926 2004) attended Cornell University and received a BS in 1948 and an LLB in 1952. He was an attorney for the ACWA from 1953-1958, becoming General Counsel of the Legal Department from 1958-1972. Sheinkman also served as
ACWA Secretary-Treasurer 1972-1976, ACTWU Secretary-Treasurer 1976-1987, ACWA Vice-President 1968-1972, and ACTWU President 1987-1995. He helped negotiate the ACTWU's merger with the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union to form the Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees(UNITE). His civic activities included serving on the Cornell University Board of Trustees, guest lecturer at the School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University, Workers Defense League, Jewish Labor Committee, American Arbitration Association, and Americans for Democratic Action.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5619: ACWA Records 5619 AV: ACTWU Audio-Visual Materials 5619 C-S MB: ACTWU President Jack Sheinkman Additional Books, Memorabilia, and Files 5619 F: ACTWU Motion Picture Films 5619 G: ACTWU Graphics 5619 MB: ACTWU Memorabilia Collection 5619 mf: ACWA Records Parts 1-3 on Microfilm 5619 OH: ACWA Oral History Project Records 5619 P: ACTWU Photographs 5619 PUBS: ACTWU Publications 5619/001: ACTWU Collective Bargaining Agreements 5619/002: ACWA Education Department Records 5619/003: ACWA Sidney Hillman Scrapbooks 5619/004 fiche: ACTWU President Jacob Sheinkman Speeches on Microfiche 5619/005: ACWA Bessie Hillman Papers 5619/006: ACTWU Executive Vice-President's Office Files 5619/007: ACTWU Organizing Department Files 5619/008: ACWA Rieve-Pollock Foundation Files 5619/009: ACTWU Operations Department Sidney Hillman Awards Files 5619/010: ACWA Jacob Potofsky files 5619/011: ACTWU Southern Regional Joint Board Files 5619/012: ACTWU Company Files 5619/013: ACTWU Research Department Correspondence Chronological Files 5619/014: ACWA Local 169 Files 5619/015: ACTWU Department of Occupational Safety and Health Files
Labor unions--New York (State)--History--20th century.; Textile workers--Labor unions--New York (State); Clothing workers--Labor unions--New York (State); Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; Sheinkman, Jacob; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; UNITE HERE (Organization)
7297023
- Locals General Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Local 2H Feinstein, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  English and Spanish
- Local 143, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  No Contents
- Local 169, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Local 340, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Locker/Abrecht Association, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Attached Paper Slip states: "See also: IUD Pension Committee"
- Art Loevy, 1985-1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Londontown Corporation, 1985-1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Lord West, 1985-1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Lowell Fever, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- M Miscellaneous, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Enclosed Folder "Tony Mazzocchi's Labor Party Proposal"
- Made in the United States of America, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Minimum Wage, 1985-1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Sub Folders "Minimum Wage" and "JS Min Wage"
- Mississippi Association of State Employees, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Multi-Fiber Arrangement (MFA), 1981-1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  English and German
- N Miscellaneous, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- National Association for the Advancement of Colored People and Legal Defense Fund, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- National Clothing Industry. Labor Management Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  1 Untitled Subfolder
- National Planning Association. Committee on New American Realities, 1985-1989 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  NPA Briefing Book Included
- NPA Board of Trustees, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Two Binders Included
- Navasky, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- New York Historical Society, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  2 Binders, 1 Large Envelope Included
- New York City Managers, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations New York State, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- New York City Mayoralty Election Campaign, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  1 Subfolder Included
- Occupational Health Legal Rights Foundation Board Meeting, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Aug. 23, 1988
- Safety and Health Department. General Correspondence, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Robert Richter Productions, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Note Inside "See also Film Fund"
- Richard Rothstein Study (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Empty
- Russia Trade, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Safety and Health Department Formaldehyde, 1984-1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Charles Sallee, 1982-1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Charles Sallee Scholarship, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- The Scheuer Foundation, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Safety and Health Department: Health and Safety Committee, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Schick Inc., 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration Environmental Network, 1985-1989 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- S Miscellaneous, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Safety and Health Department General Correspondence, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Safety and Health Department General Correspondence, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Hartmarx Pending, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  4/19/89
- Arthur Gundersheim Pending, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Arthur Goldberg Pending, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- General Executive Board Pending, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Eric Frumin Occupational Safety and Health Administration Pending (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Bernie Ferster Pending (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Garry Ferraris Pending, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Dave Dyson Pending, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Bruce Dunton, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Olga Diaz Pending, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Henrietta Dabney Pending, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Kilmer Caban Pending (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Clayola Brown Pending, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Ron Blackwell, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  8/30/89
- Irving Alter Pending, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Nick Palermo Pending, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Officers Pending, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- John Noonan Pending (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Frank Nicholas Pending (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Jo-Ann Mort, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Joyce Miller Pending (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Mazur Pending, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Arthur Loevy Pending, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- John Hudson Pending, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Nick Palermo Pending (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Harry Lautman Pending (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Labor Unity Pending (Box 3, Folder 42)
- The Kamber Group (Box 3, Folder 43)
- IUD Pending (Box 3, Folder 44)
- IUD Budget (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Dave Dyson Pending (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Al Wertheim, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Walraven Organizing Department, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Ken Wray Pending, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Nick Unger Pending, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Tom Thompson Pending (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Liz Smith Pending, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Harvey Sigelbaum Pending (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Ron Rosenberg Pending, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Research Department (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Bruce Raynor, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Bill Patterson Pending, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Organizing [1 of 3], 1987 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Organizing [2 of 3], 1989 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Organizing [3 of 3], 1988 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- P Miscellaneous, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Overseas Development Council, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Bill Patterson, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Palm Beach Incorporated, 1985-1989 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Per Capita, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Phillips Van Heusen, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Poems (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Pincus Brothers, Incorporated, 1980-1987 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Pittston (file) Coal Strike, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Resumes and Recommendations, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Regrets, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Resumes and Recommendations, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Resumes and Recommendations, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Joint Board: Buffalo, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  January 15, 1988
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Jobs With Peace Campaign, 1984-1989 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Johnson and Johnson, 1985-1988 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Jobs With Justice, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Job Training/Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Job Match, 1984-1989 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Italian American Labor Council, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Israel, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- International Textile, Garment and Leather Workers' Federation: Fifth World Congress, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Held September 26-30, 1988
- International Textile, Garment and Leather Workers' Federation: General Correspondence [1 of 2], 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- International Textile, Garment and Leather Workers' Federation: General Correspondence [2 of 2], 1989 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- International Rescue Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- International Labor Office, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- International Association of Clothing Designers, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Interco, 1987-1989 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Institute for International Economics, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- In House Polling, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Industrial Union Department Pension File, 1983-1989 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Joseph and Feiss Company, 1985-1989 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Joint Board: South Jersey, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Joint Board: Southwest Regional, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Southern Textile Regional Joint Board, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Southern New England Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Southern Regional T, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Southern Regional Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- South Carolina Coastal Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Shirt and Leisurewear Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Rochester Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Roanoke Valley Joint Board, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Quebec Joint Board, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Puerto Rico Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Pittsburgh District Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Piedmont Carolinas Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Philadelphia Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Western New York Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- North Jersey Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- New York Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Joint Board: New England, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Neckwear Workers Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Montreal Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Minnesota Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Midwest Regional Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Midwest Region, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Mid-Atlantic Region and Synthetics Division, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Mid-Atlantic Regional Joint Board, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Maine Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Joint Boards: Lehigh Valley, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Hudson Valley Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Headwear and Allied Workers Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Greater Northern Textile, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Greater Northeastern, 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Greater New York Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Glove Cities Area Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Georgia, Tennessee, Alabama (GTA) Area Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Joint Board: Eastern Pennsylvania, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Cleveland Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Joint Board: Chicago and Central States (Detroit), 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Catawba Valley Joint Board, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Canadian Office Clothing Division, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- California Joint Board Rothstein File, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Joint Board: California, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Rapid American Corporation, 1982-1985 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Asa Philip Randolph Institute, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- R Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Publix, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Public Domain, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Programs for Employment and Workplace Systems (PEWS), 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Political Letters, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Political Action Committee, 1987-1989 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Vice President's Organizing Reports, 1987-1989 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Occupational Health Forum, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Occupational Health and Safety Forum, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- O Miscellaneous, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Nuclear Freeze/Disarmament, 1986-1989 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- New York University, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- New York Times, 1985-1989 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- New York State Legislative, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- New York State Legislative City Council Endorsements, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- New York State Democratic Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- New York State Business Venture Partnership [1 of 3], 1989 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- New York State Business Venture Partnership [2 of 3], 1988 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- New York State Business Venture Partnership [3 of 3], 1987 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- New York State Executive Council Meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Social Services, 1987-1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Social Security, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Senior Citizens, 1985-1989 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Senate Banking Committee, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Schott Brothers, Incorporated, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Research Department, 1987-1991 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Research Department, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Research, 1987-1990 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Industrial Cooperation Council: Competitiveness Report, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  July 28, 1987
- Industrial Cooperation Council: Meetings, 1987-1989 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Cuomo Commission on Trade and Competitiveness, 1987-1989 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Industrial Cooperation Council: Compact, 1986-1988 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Industrial Cooperation Council: Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Industrial Areas Foundation, 1985-1990 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Import File, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- I Miscellaneous, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Headwear Division Correspondence (John Hudson), 1985-1988 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- John Hudson: Correspondence, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- John Hudson [1 of 2], 1988 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- John Hudson [2 of 2], 1989 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Homework, 1985-1989 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Holocaust, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Histadrut Dinner, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Histadrut: General Correspondence [1 of 2], 1988 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Histadrut: General Correspondence [2 of 2], 1989 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Sidney Hillman Foundation, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Health Security Action Council, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Headwear Division, 1984-1989 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Industrial Cooperation Council: Leveraged Buyout Fund, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Leveraged Buyout Fund, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Materials for Pension Meeting, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Industrial Union Department: Pension Benefit Committee, 1985-1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Industrial Union Department: Investment Project, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Industrial Union Department: Executive Council Meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Industrial Union Department: Financial Statements, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Industrial Union Department: Correspondence, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Industrial Union Department: Correspondence, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Industrial Union Department: Convention, 1986-1989 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Industrial Union Department: Constitution, 1980-1986 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Industrial Union Department: Committee on Re-Industrialization, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Industrial Union Department: Coordinated Bargaining, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Industrial Union Department: Collective Bargaining, 1985-1989 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Industrial Cooperation Council: Pension Task Force, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  Role of pensions in Mergers and Acquisitions Subcommittee, June 22, 1989
- Industrial Cooperation Council: Pension Task Force, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Industrial Cooperation Council: The New York Center for Employee Ownership and Participation, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- ALICO - Sigelbaum, 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Company, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Company, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund (Retirement Fund), 1983-1986 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund (Clofund), 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund (Clofund), 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 8)